<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<addon id="skin.madnox" version="22.10.08" name="Madnox" provider-name="Kittmaster">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.18.0" />
		<import addon="script.skin.madnox" version="1.0.5" />
		<import addon="resource.images.skin.madnox" version="1.0.1" />		
		<import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="1.0.17" />
		<import addon="plugin.video.themoviedb.helper" version="6.11.5" />
		<import addon="script.image.resource.select" version="2.0.4" />
		<import addon="script.skinvariables" version="2.1.14" />
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="8.1.2" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="16x9" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="ar_sa">مظهر غني بالميزات وقابل للتخصيص بالكامل</summary>
		<summary lang="de_de">Ein funktionsreiches und vollständig anpassbares Skin</summary>
		<summary lang="en_gb">A feature rich and fully customizable skin</summary>
		<summary lang="en_us">A feature rich and fully customizable skin</summary>
		<summary lang="es_es">Una piel rica en funciones y totalmente personalizable</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_fr">Un thème riche en fonctionnalités et entièrement personnalisable</summary>
		<summary lang="no_no">Et funksjonsrikt og fullt tilpassbart skall</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_br">Um tema rico em recursos e totalmente personalizável</summary>
		<summary lang="sv_se">Ett funktionsrikt och helt anpassningsbart skal</summary>
		<summary lang="uk_ua">Шкіра з багатими функціями та повним налаштуванням</summary>
		<description lang="ar_sa">Madnox يتميز بجمال بصري وخيارات تخصيص متعددة. هناك العديد من طرق العرض والخيارات لعرض الوسائط بالطريقة التي تريدها. جميع طرق العرض قابلة للتخصيص بالكامل. يمكنك تغيير المظهر باستخدام أنماط وسمات وخيارات مختلفة.</description>
		<description lang="de_de">Madnox steht für visuelle Attraktivität und Anpassbarkeit. Es gibt viele Ansichten und Optionen, um Ihre Medien ganz nach Wunsch zu präsentieren. Alle Ansichten sind vollständig anpassbar. Sie können das Erscheinungsbild mit verschiedenen Stilen, Themen und Optionen verändern.</description>
		<description lang="en_gb">Madnox stands for eye candy and customization. There are many different views and options to present your media in the way you want it. All views are fully customizable. You can change the look with different styles, themes and options.</description>
		<description lang="en_us">Madnox stands for eye candy and customization. There are many different views and options to present your media in the way you want it. All views are fully customizable. You can change the look with different styles, themes and options.</description>
		<description lang="es_es">Madnox destaca por su atractivo visual y personalización. Hay muchas vistas y opciones para mostrar tu contenido como prefieras. Todas las vistas son completamente personalizables. Puedes cambiar el aspecto con diferentes estilos, temas y opciones.</description>
		<description lang="fr_fr">Madnox se distingue par son esthétique et sa personnalisation. De nombreuses vues et options permettent de présenter vos médias comme vous le souhaitez. Toutes les vues sont entièrement personnalisables. Vous pouvez modifier l’apparence avec différents styles, thèmes et options.</description>
		<description lang="no_no">Madnox står for visuell appell og tilpasning. Det finnes mange visninger og alternativer for å presentere mediene dine slik du ønsker. Alle visninger kan tilpasses fullt ut. Du kan endre utseendet med ulike stiler, temaer og alternativer.</description>
		<description lang="pt_br">Madnox é sinônimo de visual atrativo e personalização. Há muitas visualizações e opções para apresentar sua mídia como quiser. Todas as visualizações são totalmente personalizáveis. Você pode alterar o visual com diferentes estilos, temas e opções.</description>
		<description lang="sv_se">Madnox står för ögongodis och anpassning. Det finns många olika vyer och alternativ för att visa ditt innehåll på det sätt du vill. Alla vyer är helt anpassningsbara. Du kan ändra utseendet med olika stilar, teman och alternativ.</description>
		<description lang="uk_ua">Madnox — це візуальна привабливість і налаштування. Існує багато варіантів перегляду та опцій для представлення медіа так, як вам подобається. Усі перегляди повністю налаштовуються. Ви можете змінити вигляд за допомогою стилів, тем і параметрів.</description>
		<disclaimer lang="ar_sa">Madnox هو خليفة Aeon Madnox من Mike_Doc وschimi2k وMeowMoo. إنه مظهر يعتمد على تصميم Aeon من djh_ وAeon Nox 4 من BigNoid وphil65. شكر خاص لـ Mr. V. جميع الحقوق محفوظة لمصممي هذه المظاهر والتعديلات.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="de_de">Madnox ist der Nachfolger von Aeon Madnox von Mike_Doc, schimi2k und MeowMoo. Es basiert auf dem Design von Aeon von djh_ und Aeon Nox 4 von BigNoid und phil65. Besonderer Dank an Mr. V. Alle Credits gehen an die Entwickler dieser Skins und Mods.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_gb">Madnox is the successor to Aeon Madnox by Mike_Doc, schimi2k and MeowMoo. It is a skin based on the design of Aeon by djh_ and Aeon Nox 4 by BigNoid and phil65. Special thanks to Mr. V. All credits to the makers of these skins and mods.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="en_us">Madnox is the successor to Aeon Madnox by Mike_Doc, schimi2k and MeowMoo. It is a skin based on the design of Aeon by djh_ and Aeon Nox 4 by BigNoid and phil65. Special thanks to Mr. V. All credits to the makers of these skins and mods.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="es_es">Madnox es el sucesor de Aeon Madnox creado por Mike_Doc, schimi2k y MeowMoo. Es un skin basado en el diseño de Aeon de djh_ y Aeon Nox 4 de BigNoid y phil65. Agradecimientos especiales a Mr. V. Todos los créditos a los creadores de estos skins y modificaciones.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="fr_fr">Madnox est le successeur d’Aeon Madnox par Mike_Doc, schimi2k et MeowMoo. Il s’inspire du design d’Aeon par djh_ et d’Aeon Nox 4 par BigNoid et phil65. Remerciements spéciaux à Mr. V. Tous les crédits vont aux créateurs de ces skins et mods.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="no_no">Madnox er etterfølgeren til Aeon Madnox av Mike_Doc, schimi2k og MeowMoo. Skallet er basert på designet til Aeon av djh_ og Aeon Nox 4 av BigNoid og phil65. Spesiell takk til Mr. V. All ære til skaperne av disse skallene og modifikasjonene.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="pt_br">Madnox é o sucessor do Aeon Madnox criado por Mike_Doc, schimi2k e MeowMoo. É um tema baseado no design do Aeon de djh_ e Aeon Nox 4 de BigNoid e phil65. Agradecimentos especiais ao Mr. V. Todos os créditos aos criadores desses temas e modificações.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="sv_se">Madnox är efterföljaren till Aeon Madnox av Mike_Doc, schimi2k och MeowMoo. Det är ett skal baserat på designen av Aeon av djh_ och Aeon Nox 4 av BigNoid och phil65. Särskilt tack till Mr. V. All ära till skaparna av dessa skal och moddar.</disclaimer>
		<disclaimer lang="uk_ua">Madnox — це наступник Aeon Madnox від Mike_Doc, schimi2k та MeowMoo. Це шкіра, заснована на дизайні Aeon від djh_ та Aeon Nox 4 від BigNoid і phil65. Особлива подяка Mr. V. Всі заслуги — авторам цих оформлень і модифікацій.</disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/forumdisplay.php?fid=314</forum>
		<source>https://github.com/kittmaster/KittmasterRepo</source>
		<website>https://github.com/kittmaster/KittmasterRepo</website>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-05.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-06.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-07.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-08.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-09.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-10.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
<news>
v.22.10.07
- Replaced PVR, channel, TV icons for updated icon set
- Repaired migrator script causing icons to point to wrong location (Rerun in advanced if you have main menu icons missing)
- Weather animation rework
v.22.10.06
- Reordered conflicting IDs causing remote control navigation jamming
- Restructured admin entry panel to include skin settings
- Created new admin menu item for advanced controls
- Added option re-run skin shortcuts migrator if conversion was unsuccesful on upgrade
- Removed multiple broken migrated navigation from refactor
v.22.10.05
- Fixed remaining rolling trailer shutoffs affecting music section
- Added missing Jump To Letter offset value to enable from refactoring for music section
v.22.10.04
- Fixed issue with migration script check in intro router
- Fixed navigation trap in "What's new" dialog
v.22.10.03
- Added missing "What's new" to the addon info dialog
v.22.10.02
- Repaired unexpected media stopping from new trailer rolling feature. Media/Music will continue uninterrupted
- Restored jump list to music section
- Restored multiple views for music specific sections i.e. missing artwork, covers etc.
- Created user selectable display for certain ratings as floating numbers or show as percent
- Reverted use of .xbt file and unpacked images per Kodi admin suggestion for addon submission
- Added missing dialog notification info if there is no biography or plot data
- Removed nav trap in 1020 view
- Consolidated identical plot methods into one singular callout			
v.22.10.01
** Front end **
- Display/Hide main context menu options
- 1st run startup will set all the default skin values if not present, ensures all controls are initialized
- Widget QOL updates, left navigations updates main page as one would expect
- Music section completely rebuilt and refactored, better artwork rendering, layout, matches video/movie/tv layouts
- Refactored infodialogs to be compartmentalized for faster loading, expansion, future growth
- Added star ratings with color selection to the movie info videoinfo line
- Revamped Media Flags to cover all the user cases, should be a major improvement
- Wikipedia user color control to the backing overlay
- Favorites overhauled with new HUD and active resizing
- Increased widgets on home screen from 6 to 20
- Widgets now have two modes, Carousel (original operation) &amp; Grid mode (new)
- Multiple "mini" system widgets to select from include CPU, GPU, Memory and others.
- Music: Converted scaling for fanart from scale to keep (User feedback: elve)			
- Built new fallback process when blur is turned off with adjustable dimming
- Blur can be fanart driven with gaussian, mixed with color, or custom color picker with alpha selected
- Complete refactor of Movie/TV show sub dialog pages
- Added custom accent color control to VideoOSD (User feedback: crazyturk)			 
- Repaired skin shortcuts for "In- Progress" movies in widgets and ALL views
- Added "In- Progress" bar overlay to all views when viewed
- Custom color selection of "In- Progress" bar globally in all views			
- New native "jump to letter" built into Kodi decoupled from Embuary Helper
- Added icons to info metadata fields for movie/TV shows rows with disable
- Added Wikipedia addon feature in detailed views
- New skin initializer for missing startup settings installer on 1st run
- Added factory restore feature resetting to 1st run out of the box values
- Added auto trailer viewer on library hover Automatic trailer video preview with fanart fill selectable			
- Video codec format type selection for media flags selection as 4K or 2160p (User feedback: lynxstrike)
- Rebuilt cinema mode and enhanced usability to include user full features (bumpers, ratings, mpaa)
- Cinema mode diagnostics with verification of path and reconstruction capability to ensure smooth user experience
- Integrating PreShow Experience for advanced Cinema Mode, allows for simple and advanced cinema experience (WIP)			
- Reformatted and updated color media flags
- Synced/Updated/Created default greyscale flags assets to match color media flags
- Moved startup logo spinner down and off large logo
- Updated missing filmstrip genre image files for completeness
- Fixed views with broken 2 and 4 thumbs to use selected fanart, fully repaired
- Jump to letter: When in "numbers", # is replaced by actual number of movie. Example 300 > 3 is showin in bar instead of #
- Poster is no longer the domanent image in views, if slider panel is selected like similar, it will display active hovered item until released

** Admin (Back end) **
- Conversion to TMDb Helper from Embuary helper completed
- Built missing code for blurring fanart images in all areas via TMDb helper
- Refactored Skin Shortcuts to remove Embuary Helper to TMDb helper link template constructors
- Custom Video Codec media flags override selector, removes skin hacking, resettable (WIP)
- Restructuring of media flags detection (WIP)
- Startup video intro controls: None, Skin built- in, Custom selectable with preview on hover
- Fixed media flags admin selector to use colored flags where screen would reset and blank out, fully repaired
- Fixed shifting color swatches shifting and showing placeholder text when disable is active
- Created "in- process" control color selection and enable control
- Controls for metadata in movies and tv shows to enable in- row icons
- Reset all skin options to default control

** General All **
- 2/16/2026 Madnox now has its own dedicated skin helper to consolidate all scripts and satisfy Kodi's requirements of free running scripts
- 2/16/2026 1st run will write all required settings (version controlled) for added dev work without prompting preventing odd behavior until restart &amp; continued use to initialize missing settings
- Multiple issues resolved (syntax, spelling, missing calls)
- Removed startup script causing forced icon view overriding all user selection (Dev leftover)
- Comprehensive removal of as many hardcoded strings into localization and all files fully translated
- Startup bugs and errors resolved
- Intro startup videos added on Kodi start.

v.22.02.06
- Added ability to turn off Madnox startup logo inside admin furniture panel
- Turned off main menu forced icons settings (dev testing left active by mistake in script)
v.22.02.05
- Fixed widgets on main screen to use custom color picker
- Subtitle color parameters can now be adjusted within the skin using custom color picker
- Remove experimental replacement dev flag until next iteration
- Minor code cleanup and refactoring
v.22.02.04
- Fixed navigation corrections to TMDb Helper page and Movie/TV Show buttons/panels.
v.22.02.03
- Removed duplicate language strings
- Fixed metadata slider and countdown timer inverted logic
- Add Norwegian language strings
v.22.02.02
- Added navigation corrections to TMDb Helper page
- Adjust default icon color include variable to correct for "icon error" where error is not present.
v.22.02.01
- * Global *
- Minor version increase to 21.02.01.
- (WIP) (Long Term) -  Begin migration from Embuary Helper to TMDb Helper. Not a trivial change, maintained as much of the physical workflow as possible, some minor changes have been made and cannot be reverted to old methods, adoption should be easily understood.
- Restructured Information dialog to support Person/Bio info into same dialog structure.
- Multiple additions to Meta data fields providing more online and local data media labels.
- Choice of large or small Madnox logo on startup.
- Added Left/Right arrows for metadata when value is greater than 8 items for visual cue.
- User adjustable time interval for Left/Right arrow slide (i.e. how often it switches if greater than 8 items).
- Added countdown timer to display Left/Right switching duration and switch point (visual cue).
- Added icons to various dialogs like "effects" for snow/leaves to visually display icon in dialog selection.
- Added Madnox logo to all dialog popups.
- Updated multiple strings to add uniqueness and better user experience diverging from cookie cutter phrases.
- Added Recommendations panel to TMDb display dialog.
- Added additional icons, feedback, graphical elements based on restructured layout to TMDb Infopage.
- Fixed aspect ratio for "Videos" and removed limit of 2 in TMDb Infopage.
- Aspect Ratio and Resolution icons colors can be set globally in the admin panel (10 options).
- Entirely retooled color picker dialog replacing Kodi's built- in version allowing slider control of RGBA.
- Local script logging enable/disable, defaults to off to prevent bloating KODI log file for debugging.
- Automatic download of baseline image collections (weather, studio etc.), can be removed or replaced as needed. Rationale: provide better start point of visuals since most users can be overwhelmed on what they should or should not use based on taste/workflow. Default download and enable will provide a better user experience and will not affect lower tier hardware as it requires minimal space requirements.
- Removed errant label in system info right side panel
- Multiple mini scripts to replicate Embuary Helper to maintain core functionality, including play all, color picker, and new feature adds.
- Added Skin Variables addons to add additional capability to replicate local related type movies and future capability updates and features.

- * Biography *
- Added death date (if applicable).
- Updated Infoline with additional icons below main title.
- Added feedback on rollover of panel data across all buttons.
- Restructured page for better flow.
- Shows local discart if movies are in focus and rollover of local movie with artwork is present.			

- * Movies *	
- Added date to main title in Information view.
- Added all relevant meta tags in grid based on TMDb Helpers tag structure retrieval.
- Updated Infoline and icons below main title with several revised icons.
- Several string updates for uniformity between dialogs
- Increased icon sizes in Infoline.			

- * TV Shows *
- Added color control to TV Show returning/air date from grey to color picker selection with persistence.
- Updated icons for returning, not returning.
- Added date to main title in Information view.
- Added all relevant meta tags in grid based on TMDb Helpers tag structure retrieval.
- Updated Infoline and icons below main title with several revised icons.
- Increased icon sizes in Infoline.

- * Music *
- Added year to Now Playing after album (if present).
- Added Aspect Ratio adjust to Admin panel to control Fanart background.
- Added switch to Now Playing script view when Play All is activated.
- (WIP) - Looking at reworking ID tag area.
</news>
	</extension>
</addon>
